### Abdallah Ibrahim

Mobile: (+20) 1124093527

E-mail: abdallanasr505@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/M45CJ3J

Xing: <a href="https://www.xing.com/profile/Abdallah Ibrahim13/cv">https://www.xing.com/profile/Abdallah Ibrahim13/cv</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdallah-ibrahim-0a2b15156/

Portfolio: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdallah-ibrahim-0a2b15156/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdallah-ibrahim-0a2b15156/</a>

# **Objective Overview:**

I am offering 3 years of experience in the web developing field (Full Stack Backend Mainly), College graduate seeking a technical position. Extensive technical experience at NTI. Motivated, enthusiastic and committed to be an added value employee at my work.

### **Personal Data:**

Name: Abdallah Nasreldin Abdelrahman Ibrahim

Date of Birth: August , 14 , 1994

Nationality: Egyptian

Interests: Traveling, playing tennis and Music

# Work experience:

- I work as PHP Laravel developer For RayaGate in Landsberger Allee
  56A 10249 Berlin, Deutschland from Mar 2023 till Now
- I work as PHP Laravel developer For JoSqual in Jordan from Feb 2023 till Mar 2023 Leaved because its way to manage its projects nonsuitable for me.
- I work as PHP Laravel developer For Resultier in twinsfall, Idaho USA from Apr 2022 till Dec 2022 Leaved due to layoff
- I worked as PHP Laravel developer as freelancer from Sep 2020 till Apr
  2022 Leaved it because of instability of monthly income and to gain more experience
- I worked as PHP developer for Euro assist form Jan 2019 till May 2019 and from Feb 2020 till Aug 2020 Leaved it due to its closing because of COVID-19 Developing the website of the company and managing its admin panel.
- I worked as Call center agent for Vodafone Egypt Sep 2016 till Oct
  2018

# Internships:

I was a trainee for Ipda3 tech for 3 Month as a Web Developer. From Nov 2019 till Jan 2020 I could Build 2 project by Laravel 5.8 and API by postman.

### **Education:**

- Nano degree in angular framework from Udacity from Jul 2022 till Aug
  2022 Graduation Project: Ecommerce Cart and products show
- Diploma in internet of thing from information Technology Institute (ITI) (https://www.iti.gov.eg/) From Jan 2021 till May 2021 My Graduation Project was about public transportation. It got the third place between all graduation projects in Graduation.
- Diploma in web Development (full stack web development PHP &Laravel): from National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) (https://www.nti.sci.eg/) from May 2019 till October 2019: good grade Graduation Project: booking system we could by it book service and knows how many time it Duarte. could get the 1st place between all projects
- Bachelor of Business Administration Faculty of commerce. Cairo University, June 2016 – good grade

#### **Technical Skills:**

Based on my Technical experience:

- front end => Angular , Bootstrap
- Back end => php/laravel and js /node.js
- Databases => Mysql and Mongo DB
- OS =>Linux (admin |), macOS
- CI/CD => Git & Github
- Familiar with Devops (AWS) & microservices & Agile methodology (ClickUp & twillo)
- Testing => TDD / PHP Unit

- Ability to deal with 3rd party API(including payment methods and gateways)
- Algorithms & data structure & Design pattern
- SOLID & OOP MOT (master of things platform) and Google Cloud platform Connecting sensor to platform using Mqtt protocol
- ERD (entity relation diagram)

### Soft Skills:

Based on my work experience & NTI & ITI and university life:

- Showing Empathy
- Quick thinking & Problem solving
- Time management: gained from my pervious and current Work.
- Team work : gained from my social work within my study in the university .
- Work under stressing: gained from my previous Work.
- Multitasks and developing myself continuously .

# **Special Training Courses:**

ICDL course Russian cultural Center summer 2014

General English Course British council summer 2015

General German Course Goethe Institute winter 2018

# **Special Skills:**

# Linguistic skills:

- Arabic: Mother tongue.
- IELTS band 6.5 (academic ).
- B1 certificate at German language (note 3)